CURRICULUM VITAE

Jalalul Mu'ti

<u>jalalul2000@gmail.com</u> | +6281357630782 | <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/jalalulmu</u> Cibadak, Kabupaten Sukabumi, Jawa Barat, 43351

PROFILE

A fresh graduate with expertise in Information Technology. A graduate of Informatics Engineering from UIN Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung. Interested in IT Support, Web Development, and Data Science. Proficient and experienced in providing effective technical support with a strong understanding of computer systems, networking, and software development.

EDUCATIONS

UIN Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung

Jawa Barat, Indonesia Sep 2020 - Dec 2024

Bachelor of Engineering in Informatics Engineering | GPA 3.82/4

- Conducted and completed research on the development of a prediction model using Machine Learning with Python for laboratory consumable needs.
- Developed the laboratory website for the Faculty of Science and Technology at UIN Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung.
- Served as a trainer and provided Microsoft Office training at PTIPD for collage students.

SMK Negeri 1 Cibadak

Kab. Sukabumi, Jawa Barat, Indonesia Jul 2017 - Apr 2020

Multimedia | 84/100

- Served as the Student Council President of SMKN 1 Cibadak for the 2018/2019 period.
- Managed the computer laboratory and successfully organized various laboratory events, including semester exams, school exams, academic selection, civil servant and PPPK selection tests, and other events.

EXPERIENCES

PT Envial Solusi Berkarya

Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Web Developer | Internship

May 2024 - Jul 2024

Developed a company profile website using WordPress.

PTIPD UIN Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung

Jawa Barat, Indonesia Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

Fullstack Web Developer | Internship

Designed the KKN website and implemented the interface based on the UI Designer's design.

• Managed the database and integrated each workflow according to the design.

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek & Traveloka

Jawa Barat, Indonesia Jul 2023 - Jan 2024

Machine Learning Cohort | Internship

Studied Artificial Intelligence (AI), specifically in the fields of machine learning and deep learning.

Developed and implemented a prediction system on mobile applications and websites.

ID/X Partners Jawa Barat, Indonesia

 $Project-Based\ Virtual\ Intern: Data\ Engineer\ ID/X\ Partners\ x\ Rakamin\ Academy\ |\ Internship$

May 2023 - Jun 2023

- Studied Data Warehouse and the ETL process used in data warehousing.
- Completed a data warehousing case study using the ETL process with Talend Application.

CV Kawatama Sinergi

Jawa Barat, Indonesia

Graphic Designer | Internship

Jul 2019 - Oct 2019

- Designed banners, website icons, and website illustrations.
- Created mobile application design mockups.

CERTIFICATIONS

- CERTIFIED INTERNATIONAL SPECIALIST in DATA ENGINEERING (Foundation), PASAS Institute, No. CISDE14851, December 2024
- CERTIFIED INTERNATIONAL SPECIALIST in DATA VISUALIZATION (Foundation), PASAS Institute, No. CISDV14400, February 2024
- Network Security, Cisco Networking Academy, January 2024
- CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks, Cisco Networking Academy, December 2022
- Microsoft Office Specialist (Office Word 2016), Certiport, Verify. wB9pk-22XH, November 2022

SKILLS

Problem Solving, Patience, Adaptability, Attention to Detail; PHP, SQL, Graphic Design, Hardwere, Network; Laravel, Adobe, Figma